The weakening of the human connection to nature might be good for economic growth but is bad for people.
人与自然的联系减弱，或许有利于经济增长，却对人有害。
A tipping point was reached in 2020 when human-made materials—such as steel, concrete and plastic—were found to weigh more than all life on Earth.
2020年，一个临界点到来了：人们发现，钢铁、混凝土和塑料等人造材料比地球上全部生物加起来还要重。
Continuing to grow concrete forests rather than real ones is shortsighted.
继续种植“混凝土森林”而非真正的森林，是目光短浅的。
Simply being in the nearest wood has such health benefits that the Woodland Trust successfully lobbied for it to be prescribed by doctors.
单是待在离自己最近的树林里，就对健康大有益处，林地信托因此成功游说，让医生可以把它当作处方开给病人。
Yet slipping from popular culture is the wonder and beauty of the natural world.
然而，自然界的奇妙与美正从流行文化中淡出。
For every three nature-related words in hit songs of the 1950s, researchers found, there was only slightly more than one 50 years later.
研究人员发现，20世纪50年代的热门歌曲中每出现三个与自然相关的词，50年后的热门歌曲中只有略多于一个。
It is not a moment too soon that teenagers will be able to take a natural history test, given that for decades children have been able to name more video game characters than wildlife species.
鉴于几十年来孩子们能叫出名字的电子游戏角色一直比野生动物物种还多，青少年即将可以参加自然史考试，实在是早该如此。
Part of remedying this social disease would be for parliament to pass a “right to grow” law, allowing anyone to turn underused public spaces into vegetable and fruit gardens.
治疗这种社会病的举措之一，可以是由议会通过一项“种植权”法，允许任何人把未充分利用的公共空间改造成果蔬园。
The idea is for people to get back in touch with the soil—while producing food sustainably.
这样做的用意是让人们重新亲近土壤，同时以可持续的方式生产食物。
Vegetable planting has a respectable tradition.
种菜有着值得尊重的传统。
In April 1649, locals responded to high prices and food shortages by cultivating vegetables on common land in southern England.
1649年4月，当地人在英格兰南部的公地上种植蔬菜，以应对物价高涨和粮食短缺。
The practice of throwing seed bombs to turn vacant plots of land green took off in 1970s New York, and has been revived by green-thumbed social media influencers who defy local U.S. regulations in a war on ugly spots in cities.
投掷种子炸弹、让一块块空地变绿的做法，在20世纪70年代的纽约流行起来；如今，一些擅长园艺的社交媒体网红又让这种做法重获新生，他们无视美国的地方法规，向城市里那些难看的地方开战。
Apart from the urgent task of providing more healthy nutrients to those who increasingly can’t afford them, publicly accessible fruit and vegetable gardens connect what we eat to where it comes from—the means of production, if you will.
向公众开放的果蔬园肩负着一项紧迫任务：有些人越来越负担不起有益健康的营养物质，要为他们多提供这些营养；除此之外，这些果蔬园还能把我们吃的东西与它的来源联系起来，这个来源，不妨称之为“生产资料”。
They can make unlovely spaces lovely, and marry use and beauty as well as help promote a sense of community.
它们能让难看的空间变得赏心悦目，把实用与美观结合起来，还能帮助增强社区意识。
Plants are also, of course, our first defence against species loss and climate change.
当然，植物也是我们抵御物种消失和气候变化的第一道防线。
Such planting is a small step for humanity—in the right direction.
这样的种植对人类而言是一小步——而且是朝着正确方向迈出的一步。